1. ✦Alone Among the Stars✦
By Takuma Okada | noroadhome.itch.io

2. A solo roleplaying game about exploring fantastic planets

3. You are a solitary adventurer, hopping from planet to planet exploring. Each world has unique features for you to discover and record. They are represented by cards from a standard deck, placed face down.

4. To find a new planet, roll a six-sided die and place cards face down equal to the number rolled.

5. To flip over a card to discover something, roll a six-sided die:

6. On a 1-2 it is arduous to get to.
On a 3-4 you come upon it suddenly.
On a 5-6 you spot it as you are resting.

7. The suit and rank determine the discovery. In your ship’s log (a small journal if you have one), record a short description and your reaction in a few sentences, and roll for the next card. Each time you complete a planet, give it a number or a name, and find a new planet.

8. Play until you are tired, and want to return home. If you want to remember your travels, save the journal. If the memories bring you pain, burn it.


9. ⯁ Diamonds 
Diamonds are living beings: People like or unlike you, fish, dinosaurs, wolves, birds, giant insects, etc.

10. ♣ Clubs  
Clubs are plants and other immobile forms of life: Towering trees, carnivorous pitchers, giant ferns, glowing weeds, floating flowers, oozing mushrooms, etc.

11. ♥ Hearts 
Hearts are ruins: Mysterious obelisks, vine-covered temples, abandoned dwellings for people bigger than you, a wrecked spaceship, etc.

12. ♠ Spades 
Spades are natural phenomena: Huge crystal formations, mirages, vividly colored lightning, strange clouds, rocks eroded in strange shapes, veins of precious metals, etc.

13.
A: In a field taller than you.
2: Under the light of the moon(s).
3: By a gentle river.
4: In a steep canyon.
5: In a treetop.
6: On the snowy peak of a mountain.
7: Near a volcano.
8: On a glacier.
9: Deep underground.
10: On a cliff face.
J: In the desert.
Q: In deep water.
K: Floating in the air.
